<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- This refers to add-ons that can be purchased within the app, also known as extensions or
        plug-ins. -->
    <string name='add_ons'>Add-Ons</string>

    <string name='manual_sort_order'>Manual Sort Order</string>
    <string name='manual_sort'>Manual Sort</string>
    <string name='manual_sort_ui_change'>When the manual sort order is the first item here, then
        pressing the sort button in the task list will enter manual sort mode.  You can still
        return to this screen by choosing the \"Sort Order\" menu option.</string>
    <string name='sort_order_set_incorrectly'>In order to sort manually, the first sort order option
        for this view must be set to the manual sort order.  Would you like to fix this now?</string>
    <string name='incorrect_sort_order'>Incorrect Sort Order</string>
    <string name='manual_sort_instructions'>Drag the tasks to reorder</string>
    <string name='license'>License</string>
    <string name='upgraded_license'>Upgraded License</string>
    <string name='license_description'>Unlocks the app so it can be used beyond the trial
        period.</string>
    <string name='upgraded_license_description'>Easier license management. Uses an in-app purchase
        instead of a separate download.</string>
    <string name='manual_sort_add_on'>Manual Sort Add-On</string>
    <string name='manual_sort_description'>Allows you to specify your own sort order for
        tasks. Includes synchronization.</string>
    <string name='tap_on_item'>Tap on an item to learn more.</string>
    <string name='purchased'>Purchased</string>
    <string name='purchased_with_checkmark'>&#x2713; Already Purchased</string>
    <string name='buy_now'>Buy Now</string>
    <string name='buy'>Buy</string>
    <string name='manual_sort_not_purchased'>You will need to purchase the manual sort add-on in
        order to specify your own sort order.</string>
    <string name='learn_more'>Learn More</string>
    <string name='add_on_missing'>Add-On Missing</string>
    <string name='sort_order_'>Sort Order...</string>
    <string name='subtasks_must_be_indented'>Because the first sort order for this view is set to
        manual sort, subtasks will be indented for manual sorting to work properly.</string>
    <string name='subtasks_hidden_if_parent_hidden'>Because the first sort order for this view is
        set to manual sort, subtasks whose parents are filtered out will not be visible. This is
        necessary for manual sorting to work properly.</string>
    <string name='unable_to_sort'>Unable to Sort</string>
    <string name='must_be_in_same_account'>The tasks being sorted must be linked to the same
        account.</string>
    <string name='manual_sort_on_long_press'>Long press triggers manual sort</string>
    <string name='first_sort_order_manusl'>When first sort order is set to manual sort</string>
    <string name='sign_in_needed'>Sign-in needed. Check your notification area.</string>

    <string name='upgrade_license_long_description'>
        <![CDATA[
            <p>You can upgrade your license to an in-app purchase and eliminate the need to enter a
                registration code or download a separate app that holds the license.  The upgraded
                license works on all of your Android devices - including smartphones and tablets -
                and travels with the app automatically as you upgrade or replace devices.</p>
            <p>This is an optional upgrade. You can continue to enter a registration code or download
                the separate license even though it has been de-listed.</p>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name='manual_sort_long_description'>
        <![CDATA[
            <p>The manual sort add-on gives you the ability to choose your own sort order.  Once
                purchased, you can drag and drop tasks within a list to set their order.</p>
            <p><b>How to Perform Manual Sorting:</b></p>
            <p>When viewing a task list, go to the sort order options and choose \"Manual Sort
                Order\" as the first sort order.  Once this is done, you can either select the
                \"Manual Sort\" command from the task list or tap on the sort order button to
                begin sorting your tasks.  Tasks are sorted by dragging and dropping them into their
                new locations.</p>
            <p>An option is also available in the Viewing and Editing section of the settings to
                perform sorting by long-pressing on a task.</p>
            <p><b>Google Synchronization:</b></p>
            <p>The manual sort order will synchronize with Google Tasks, but with a few limitations.
                Google keeps track of the sort order at the folder level, and Ultimate To-Do List
                keeps track of the sort order at the account level. This means that views that
                display tasks from multiple folders (such as the Hotlist or All Tasks list), will
                not show tasks in the exact same order that you see when logged into your Google
                account from a web browser.  When viewing a single folder from Ultimate To-Do List,
                the views will be in sync.</p>
            <p>The sort order of subtasks will be fully in sync with Google\'s web interface. The
                sort order also syncs fully with multiple devices.</p>
            <p><b>Toodledo.com Synchronization:</b></p>
            <p>Toodledo does not offer manual sorting capability.  However, the manual sort order
                will synchronize with multiple devices running Ultimate To-Do List that are linked
                to the same Toodledo account.  Toodledo does allow the sort order information to
                pass through its servers.</p>
            <p>Toodledo does offer the ability to specify a sort order for subtasks.  However, due
                to limits in the interface Toodledo provides to mobile apps, this sort order cannot
                be synchronized.</p>
            <p>Note that Toodledo tasks will start out in an unsorted state.  Until you have
                specified a sort order, tasks may appear in a different order on different
                devices.</p>
        ]]>
    </string>
</resources>