<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name='shutdown_msg'
        >If you\'re too busy to read this important message now, you can view it in the
        Help area later.\n

        \nIn July of 2024, we notified our users about the need to raise additional revenue to
        keep this app on Google Play, in order to cover increased overhead imposed by Google. We
        conducted a survey to help us decide our next step. We received many positive responses
        about the app\'s usefulness, but there was insufficient interest in paying for an annual
        subscription or adding more intrusive advertising. As a result, we will be unpublishing
        the app from Google Play on February 28, 2025.\n

        \nAfter the app is unpublished, it will continue to work on your device. However, you
        will not be able to install the app from Google Play on any new devices. To allow you to
        continue using the app, we have published a downloadable installer on our website. You
        will find the download link in the app\'s Help section. Distributing the app in this way
        will allow us to continue making it available at a fraction of the cost we incur with
        Google.\n

        \nAll paid add-ons have been unlocked within the app, so you can now access them at no
        charge. If you purchased a paid add-on on or after January 1, 2023, send us an email
        and we will issue a refund upon request.\n

        \nGoing forward, updates to the app will be limited to critical bug fixes only. While
        we cannot predict the future, at this time we have no reason to believe the app will
        stop working as new Android versions are released in the coming years. One potential
        issue would be if Toodledo or Google make changes to their tasks interface that requires
        corresponding changes on our side. If these changes are extensive, then it may not be
        possible for us to make the needed updates. We will keep you updated through the website:
        https://customsolutions.us/utl\n

        \nIf you\'re a software developer and are interested in using our code as the basis for
        your own app, we have published the source code on GitHub. You can find a link to the
        repository in the Help area.
    </string>

    <!-- New strings for help screen: -->
    <string name='removal_soon'>About the upcoming removal from Google Play</string>
    <string name='download_latest'>Download Latest Version</string>
    <string name='contact_by_email'>Contact Us By Email</string>
    <string name='view_source'>View Source Code</string>
    <string name='view_source2'>Visit the app\'s repository on GitHub</string>
</resources>