<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name='survey_header'>Important Information</string>
    <string name='help_us_keep'>Help keep the app on Google Play</string>
    <string name='survey_description' examples='Ultimate To-Do List'
        >If you\'re too busy to read this important message now, you can view it in the Help
        area later.\n

        \n%1$s is at a crossroads. Increasing overhead imposed by Google to stay compliant with
        policy and to accommodate behavior changes in new versions of Android are making it
        impossible for us to maintain the app without additional revenue. The
        current system that uses a combination of non-intrusive banner ads and one-time purchases
        is insufficient. Without additional revenue, the app will eventually be removed from
        Google Play.\n

        \nWe are asking for feedback from our long-term users to help us decide how to proceed.
        We specifically want to know if you would be willing either pay a small annual fee or
        accept more intrusive ads (such as popups) in order to continue using the app. In
        exchange we would promise to both maintain the app and release new features at a minimum
        of once per year. Also, all of the existing paid add-ons would be offered at no
        additional cost.\n

        \nIn the following 3 question survey, we will ask you what you would be willing to do
        and what new features you are most interested in.
    </string>
    <string name='dont_ask_again'>Don\'t Ask Again</string>
    <string name='start_survey'>Start Survey</string>

    <string name='survey'>Survey</string>
    <string name='survey_q1'>Question 1 of 3: What would you be willing to pay annually
        to maintain access to the app and receive new features?</string>
    <string name='pay_up_to' examples='$5.00'>I would pay up to %1$s per year.</string>
    <string name='rather_have_ads'>I won\'t pay, but am willing to have more intrusive ads, such
        as popups.</string>
    <string name='no_ads_or_purchases'>Neither. I would rather switch to another app.</string>
    <string name='next'>Next</string>
    <string name='back'>Back</string>

    <string name='survey_q2'>Question 2 of 3: What new features would you be interested in?
        (Check all that apply.)</string>
    <string name='wear_task_creation'>Ability to create new tasks using the Wear OS app.</string>
    <string name='voice_support'>Support for voice entry in languages other than English.</string>
    <string name='task_dependencies'>The ability to specify when one task depends on
        another.</string>
    <string name='modern_ui'>Modernization of the user interface.</string>
    <string name='checklists'>Resettable checklists (grocery list, packing list, etc.)</string>
    <string name='more_sync_options'>An additional sync option, such as to Google Drive or a new
        service we create. This would be cheaper than a paid Toodledo account, avoid the bugs
        and limitations of Google Tasks, and allow all features of the app to be available and
        synchronized across devices. For example, this option would support subtasks of subtasks
        and sync of custom views. A disadvantage of this option is that there would be no
        web-based interface for managing tasks on a computer, although you could use an Android
        emulator for this.</string>
    <string name='other_features'>Other features you would like to see:</string>
    <string name='no_features'>I\'m not interested in new features.</string>
    <string name='please_select_option'>Please select an option.</string>

    <string name='survey_q3'>Question 3 of 3: Among the new features you selected, which one
        would be the highest priority for you?</string>
    <string name='survey_q3_2'>Question 3 of 3 (optional): If you have any other feedback,
        feel free to include it here:</string>
    <string name='more_sync_options2'>More sync options.</string>
    <string name='the_other_features'>The other features I specified.</string>
    <string name='other_feedback'>If you have any other feedback, include it here:</string>
    <string name='submit_survey'>Submit My Answers</string>

    <string name='submitting'>Submitting…</string>
    <string name='survey_submitted'>Your answers have been submitted. Thanks for the
        feedback! We will post an update in the app when we have decided on next steps.</string>
    <string name='technical_error'>Sorry, a technical error occurred.</string>
    <string name='network_error'>Can\'t connect. Check your internet connection.</string>
</resources>